快点啊各位  飞机4小时后就起飞了
You guys, hurry up! The flight leaves in 4 hours!
可能要很久才能叫到车
It could take time to get a texi,
可能又会遇到大塞车
there could be traffic!
飞机可能会提早起飞
The plane could leave early!
等我们抵达伦敦
When we get to London,
入境时可能会大排长龙  快点
there could be a line at customs! Come on!
去伦敦六小时的航班  够她念了
Six-hour trip to London. That's a lot of Monica.
护照  打勾  相机  打勾
Passport, check. Camera, check.
旅行支票  打勾
Traveler's checks, check.
-你在叫谁打勾  -我自己
- Who are you saying "check" to? - Myself.
以此提醒我没落东西
You know, for remembering to pack a thing.
做好一件事就打个勾勾
You do a good thing, you get a "check."
这是我妈的习惯  我没想过很怪
My mom does it. I never realized it was weird.
我妈曾经把头塞进烤箱里
My mom used to put her head in the oven.
其实只有一次  不过还是蛮怪的
Actually, she only did it the one time. But it's pretty weird.
准备好了吗
Are you ready yet?
-好了  机票带了吗  -在这里  打勾
- Yep. You got the tickets? - Oh, got it right here. Check!
去伦敦咯  宝贝
It's all London, baby!
来一张
Here we go.
你的护照拿了吗[你有护照吗]
You got your passport?
有啊  梳妆台第三个抽屉
Yeah, my third drawer of my dresser.
弄丢就糟了
You don't want to lose that!
可算明白了
There it is!
如果你要用真空吸尘器的话
Okay, if you need the vacuum,
就在我的柜子里的左手边
it's in my closet on the left-hand side.
垃圾袋在冰箱旁边
Garbage bags are next to the refrigerator.
等下  瑞秋也会在家
Okay, wati. Rachel's gonna be here, too.
我不能问她吗
Can't I just ask her the stuff?
好啊  你问她吧
Yeah, okay. Give that a try!
-走了  -好耶
- Let's do it. - Cheerio!
伦敦  宝贝
London, baby!
我绝对"不会"觉得烦
That's not gonna get annoying.
伦敦  宝贝
London, baby!
你知道吗  我错了
You know what? I was wrong.
人都到了  那我们该出发了
We're all here. I guess we should get going!
我很想过去抱你一下
I want to come over there and give you a hug
祝福你婚礼顺利
and wish you luck at your wedding,
但是我不想  没法起来
but I don't--can't get up.
那我过去抱你
Oh, I'll come hug you.
太好了  帮我拿下报纸好吗
Great, yeah, can you bring me the newspaper?
-快快乐乐地结婚吧  -谢谢
- Have a great wedding. - Thanks.
钱德勒  我也想抱你
Chandler, I want to hug you too!
好  顺便去把我的书拿来
Oh, great. You might as well bring me my book.
就在你们房间的餐桌上
It's on the counter of your apartment.
我们要走了
So we're off.
-玩得开心点  -多谢
- Have fun! - Thanks.
-真不敢相信你居然不能去  -是啊
- I can't believe you won't be there. - I know.
-那就去嘛  你为什么不去呢  -什么
- So, come. Why don't you come? - What?
伦敦啊  来伦敦吧  求求你了
To London. Come to London. Please?
我真的很希望你去
It would mean so much to me.
我要工作  对不起
I gotta work. I'm sorry.
你为什么不能请几天假
Why can't you take a couple of days off?
因为他们不批准  我跟你说过我去不了
Because I can't. I told you, "No, I can't."
这可是我的婚礼啊
This is my wedding.
说真的  真的迟到了
You know what? Now we really are late.
快走  快走  快走
Let's go. Let's go, let's go!
好吧  回来再让你看录影带
Fine, you'll watch it on video when we get back.
菲比  你的书书  苏苏
Here you go, Phoebe! Phoe-bo! Phoo-ba-la!
乖
You!
好了  走吧
All right. Let's go!
菲比  再见
Bye, Pheebs!
再见
Bye
伦敦  宝贝
London, baby!
天呐
Oh, God!
你要抱抱吗
Do you need a hug?
你不必帮我拿东西
You don't have to bring me anything.
钱德勒  做点动作
Chandler, do something!
配合下嘛  做动作啊
Come on. Do something!
我有啊  我在忽视你
I am. I'm ignoring you.
好吧  我来上镜头
I'll be the on-camera guy.
好  第一站
All right. First stop
西敏寺
Westminster Abbey.
那是什么鬼东西
Oh, what the hell is that?
伦敦啊  宝贝
That's London, baby!
好  酒店在这里
All right, the hotel's here.
等一下
Wait.
不对  我们要去
No, we want to go...
不  我知道了
No. I know.
我得进入地图里
I'm gonna have to go into the map.
要是里面有个小钱德勒  杀了它
If you see a little version of me in there, kill it!
我知道了
I got it.
走吧
Here we go!
好吧  听着  听着
Ok, listen, listen.
我们不是得一直这样逛大街吧
We're not gonna have to walk this way the entire time, are we?
你害我又乱了啦
Man, you made me lose it!
那时十点都没到
That was all before 10:00.
厨师打电话来说
The caterer rang to say
龙高鸡换成基辅鸡
it's gonna be Chicken Kiev instead of Chicken Tarragon.
然后花匠打电话说没有郁金香了
Then the florist phoned to say there aren't any tulips.
然后大提琴手得了手腕隧道症候群
And the cellist has carpal tunnel syndrome...
艾蜜莉  亲爱的  好吗
Emily, honey. Okay?
我也去你妈的
Well, up yours too!
什么
what?
-不是  这是暂停的意思  -对不起
- No, no! That's "time out." - Sorry.
宝贝  放轻松
Sweetie, you got to relax.
一切都会很美好的
Everything's gonna be great, okay?
走吧
Come on, come on.
基辅鸡
Chicken Kiev?
临时能有这道菜不错吧
Doesn't that sound delicious at the last minute?
是啊  但像鲑鱼什么的
You know, but something like salmon
会比鸡肉有档次的多
would be more elegant than chicken.
也不必担心沙门氏茵
And you wouldn't worry about the salmonella.
真想赶快看到婚礼场地
So I can't wait to see where you're getting married.
是啊是啊  那个地方很美
Yeah, yeah. This place is beautiful.
艾蜜莉的父母就在那里结婚的
Emily's parents got married here.
我还是不敢相信它居然要被拆了
I still can't believe they're tearing it down.
绝对是你这辈子见过的最美丽的建筑
It really is the most lovely building you'll ever see.
就在那
I mean, it's over...
天呐
Oh, my God!
还不错
It's nice.
我的天呐
Oh, my God!
怎么会这样  我们该怎么办
How could this be happening? What are we gonna do?
放心  不会有问题的
It's all right. Everything's gonna be all right.
怎么会没问题
How is it gonna be all right?
嗯  说得也是
Uh-hah. I see that.
好吧  我问了一个拿铁锹的哥们儿
Okay. I talked to a guy with a shovel,
知道怎么回事了
and I found out what happened.
-怎么回事  -怎么回事
-what?  -what?
拆除提前进行了
They tore it down a few days early.
漂亮
All right!
西敏寺
Westminster Abbey.
我宣布  这绝对是我见过最美的教堂
Hands down, best abbey I ever seen.
你觉得西敏寺如何  钱德勒
What do you think of the Abbey, Chandler?
很漂亮  很漂亮
Yean, I think it's great! It's great.
不过  他们正打算改名
You know, they're thinking of changing the name of this place.
真的吗  改成什么
Really? To what?
改成"把摄影机收起来"
To "Put the Camera Away"!
你真是"西敏怒汉"
Man, you are Westminster Crabby.
亲爱的  别起来  你需要什么
Honey, don't get up. What do you need?
没什么
Nothing.
拜托  我就是留下来照顾你的
Come on. I'm here to take care of you.
你想要什么  我什么都可以帮你
What do you need? Anything.
好吧  我要提一下内裤
Okay, I have a wedgie.
好吧  真有你的风格
Okay, that is all you.
你中午想吃什么
What do you want for lunch?
我不知道
Oh, I don't know.
我们是得吃饭
I guess we have to eat.
我一定要吃
Yeah, I do.
怎么了
What's the matter?
我和罗斯之间的事弄得真差劲
I'm bummed the way I left things with Ross.
真后悔骗他说我要工作  他好像很气我
I wish I didn't lie about work. He seemed so mad at me.
别太苛责自己
Don't be so hard on yourself.
如果我依然深爱着的人要结婚的话
If someone I was still in love with was getting married--
依然深爱着的
Still in love with?
-对啊  -我才没有爱着罗斯
- Yeah. - I'm not in love with Ross.
没有啊  很好
No, no. Good!
我也没有
Yeah, me neither.
菲比  我不去参加婚礼
Phoebe, I'm not at the wedding
是因为他是我的前男友
because he's my ex-boyfriend
去了会很不自在
and that would be really uncomfortable.
不是因为我还爱他
Not because I'm in love with him.
我对他的感觉和其他人一样
I like Ross as much as next guy.
显然  我是对他有感觉
Clearly, I have feelings for him,
但那不是爱
but feelings don't mean love.
我对罗斯还有爱的感觉吗  有
I mean, do I still have loving feelings for Ross? Yeah!
我一直都有感觉
I have continuing feelings of love.
但那并不表示我还爱着他
But that doesn't mean I'm still in love with him.
我对他还有"性"趣  可我确实很爱他
I have sexual feelings for him, but I do love him.
天呐
Oh, my God!
你为什么不告诉我
Why didn't you tell me?
-我们以为你知道  -你们
- We thought you knew! - We?
对  我们都知道  还经常在聊
We all know. We talk about it all the time.
你们都知道  罗斯知道吗
You all know? Does Ross know?
不  罗斯什么都不知道
No! Ross doesn't know anything.
真不敢相信你们居然没告诉我
Cannot believe you didn't tell me!
因为我们以为你知道  那么明显
We thought you knew. It's so obvious!
天啊  这就好比告诉莫妮卡
God! It would be like telling Monica,
"喂  你很爱干净哦"
"Hey, you know, you like things clean."
你们想买什么
So what do you find in the market for?
有围巾  纪念明信片
We got scarves, souvenir postcards...
瞧瞧这个  怎么样
Check this out! Huh?
真心不错  你觉得呢
That's the stuff! What do you think?
我就不用再买
I'm not gonna have to buy
印着"与笨蛋同行"的T恤了
that "I'm with a stupid" T-shirt anymore.
我喜欢  给你钱
Well, I like it. Here you go.
你不是真打算买的  对吧
You're not really buying that, are you?
你不觉得你今天已经让我够难堪了吗
Don't you think you've embarrassed me enough for one day?
哦  我让你难堪了吗
Oh, I embarrass you?
叫我怎么回答  我一直都在假装根本不认识你
How can I answer when I'm pretending I don't know you?
他是在嫉妒  你戴着很好看
He's just jealous. You fit it right.
伦敦人都戴这个
All Londoners wear them.
是吗  那这里怎么没人戴
Really? Then how come no one here anywhere is wearing one?
他们都是观光客
They're all tourists.
如果你要当街戴着那顶帽子
If you insist on wearing that in public,
下午你就自己去逛
you're gonna spend the afternoon all by yourself.
如果你逼我在你和帽子之间做选择
If you make me choose between you and the hat,
我选择帽子
I choose the hat.
-够英明  -谢了
- Good choice. - Thanks.
够了  行吧
That's it! Okay?
我要走了  我不想再丢脸了
I'm out of here. I'm not gonna be embarrassed any more.
-有人吗  -嗨
- Hello?  - Hey!
我刚跟你爸谈过  你猜怎样
I just spoke to your dad, and you know what?
他好像觉得
He seems to think
我们可以重新找一个婚礼场地
we'll be able to find a new place for the wedding.
-不必了  -你找到地方了吗
- We don't have to. - You found a place?
没有  但莫妮卡和我讨论过
No, but Monica and I were talking
我因为礼堂被拆的事很烦
and I was so upset about the hall being knocked down
然后她建议把婚礼推迟几天
and she suggested that we just put the wedding off for a bit.
她说什么
She said what?
她说如果我不满意在一个
She said if I'm not gonna be happy getting married
临时找到的地方结婚
somewhere that we can find in a day,
我们就应该延期
well, then we should just postpone it.
延期
Postpone it.
艾蜜莉  你觉得莫妮卡知道
Emily, do you think Monica realizes
我们爸妈为这场婚礼花了多少钱吗
how much our parents spent on this wedding?
你觉得我妹的小脑袋
Do you think my sister's teeny, tiny, little brain
能理解大家特地挪出时间
comprehends that people took time out of their lives
不远千里坐飞机来这里吗
to fly thousands of miles to be here?
这么做是不对的
This isn't right.
我知道大家会失望
I realize that people are gonna be disappointed.
但等我们准备好了  他们一定会再来的
But I'm sure they'll come back when we can do it right.
我不能叫人家这么做  你会吗
I can't ask people to do that. Would you ask people to do that?
别拿你的裤子指着我
Don't you point your pants at me!
我们别无选择
We have no choice.
像样一点的场地
Anywhere that's half-decent
肯定在几个月前就被预定了
will have been booked months ago.
罗斯  你还不明白吗
Ross, don't you understand?
我现在在说的可是我们的婚礼啊
This is our wedding I'm talking about!
我只知道延期是不可能的
The only thing I understand is postponing it is not an option.
我们只能现在结婚
This is when we're getting married.
那你现在什么意思  今天不结就拉到吗
So what do you say? It's now or never?
不对  我是说今天就结
No, I'm saying it's now.
-否则呢  -我没说否则
- Or? - There's no "or" in mine!
这条裤子是怎么搞的
What is wrong with these pants?
不是裤子  是你本末倒置
It's not the pants. It's you who's backwards.
要是你不懂这件事对我多重要
If you don't understand how important this is to me,
也许我们根本就不该结婚
well, then, perhaps we shouldn't be getting married at all!
艾蜜莉  等一下  别走
Emily, no! Wait, stop! Emily, please...
购物有没有让你忘掉对罗斯的爱
So...Did shopping help you feel any better about Ross?
曼哈顿的店不够多
Manattan doesn't have enough stores.
我觉得我可以帮你忘了他
I think I can help you get over him.
真的吗
You can?
对  我需要你给我拿几张罗斯的照片
Yeah, I just need you to bring me some photos of Ross
一小块巧克力
and a small piece of chocolate
和一杯温水
and a glass of tepid water.
是不是那种巫术啊
Oh, is this one of those things
你要把他的一些物件
where you throw a bunch of his stuff
跟墓地的土装在一个袋子里
in a bag with some graveyard dirt
然后挂在一棵面北的树上
and hang it on a north-facing tree?
除非你也在打隔的话
Only if you have the hiccups too.
照片是给你的
Yeah, the picures are for you.
巧克力和水是给我的
The chocolate and water is for me.
我只是不想起来
I just didn't feel like getting up.
我要给你看一张罗斯的照片
Okay. I'm gonna show you a picture of Ross, okay?
而你要去回忆
And you're going to remember
他不好的地方  明白吗
all the bad things about him, all right?
-专心想他的缺点  -没问题
- Really focus on his flaws. - I can do that.
我们交往时我就这么做过
Certainly I did that while we were going out.
在开始之前
Before we get started,
我想先声明  我爱罗斯
I just want to say, for the record, that I love Ross.
我觉得他真的是个好小伙
I think he is such a great guy.
好  现在闭上眼睛
Okay. Now, close your eyes.
想像你跟罗斯在一起
And imagine that you're with Ross.
想像你在吻他
Imagine that you're kissing him.
你的手在他身上游走
You're running your hands all over his body.
你的手抚弄他的头发  但是
You run your hands through his hair but...
好恶心  是某种油
Gross! It's some kind of grease.
我不知道
I don't know.
他的头发没那么招人烦
His hair never bothered me that much.
那应该算是硬而不是油
It was more crunchy than it was greasy.
好吧  比我想得难多了
This will be harder than I thought.
试试"厌恶疗法"好了
Let's try some aversion therapy.
看着照片
Look at the picture.
现在觉得怎样
How do you feel now?
我比较不喜欢你了
Well, I like you less.
抱歉
Sorry.
我才抱歉  我之前真不该说你丢我的脸
I'm sorry. I really shouldn't have said you were embarrassing me.
真的很过份
That really wasn't cool.
如果你会高兴一点  我今天过得很悲惨
And if it makes you feel any better, I've had a really lousy day.
我也是
Me too.
-真的吗  -才怪
- Yeah? - No!
我玩得超过瘾的
I had the best day ever!
老兄  你来看
Dude, check this out!
跟我的朋友打个招呼
So say hi to my friend,
告诉他你喜欢我的帽子
tell him you like my hat.
-好  你朋友叫什么名字  -钱德勒
- Okay. So what's your friend's name? - Chandler.
钱德勒你好
Hi, Chandler.
-那是  -那是小弗啦  宝贝
- That's... - That's Fergie, baby!
乔伊说你不喜欢他的帽子
Joey says you don't really like his hat,
但我觉得蛮时鬃的
but I think it's kind of dashing.
你是怎么  你什么时候
How did you--when did you--
我想搞清楚去白金汉宫的路
I was trying to get to Buckingham Palace.
所以我就走进地图  然后
So I'm in my map and...
听说你和艾蜜莉谈过
I understand you had a little talk with Emily.
没错
Yes, I did.
不用谢我
And you are welcome.
谢你
Am I?
是你提议把婚期延后的
Was it your idea to postpone the wedding?
-我要上厕所  -等我
- I'm going to the bathroom. - Wait up!
既然你这么会解决问题  问题来了
Since you're the fix-it lady, here's a pickle:
当新娘说她根本不想结婚时
What do you do when the bride says
你打算怎么办
she doesn't want to have the wedding at all?
-她这么说了吗  -对啊
- She said that? - Yeah.
为什么
Why?
不知道
I don't know.
我跟她说因为礼堂被拆而延期
I told her it was stupid to put off the wedding
是个蠢主意
just because the hall was gone,
她就被气跑了
and she, like, flipped out.
天呐  你比我还笨
Oh, my God! You're even dumber than I am.
什么
Excuse me?
你筹备这次婚礼多久了
How long have you been planning this wedding?
不好说  一个月吧
I don't know. A month?
艾蜜莉可能从五岁起就在计划了
Emily's probably been planning it since she was 5.
从她第一次拿来一个枕套
Ever since the first time she took a pillowcase
披在脑袋后面开始
and hung it off the back of her head.
我们女生都这样
That's what we did.
我们梦想办一场完美的婚礼
We dreamed about the perfect wedding.
在一个完美的场地
In the perfect place.
有一个完美的四层结婚蛋糕
With the perfect four-tiered wedding cake.
上面有小人偶
With the little people on top.
但最重要的是
But the most important part
有个完美的男人
is that we had the perfect guy
而他正好了解这一切对我们有多重要
who understood just how important all that other stuff was.
我都不知道
I had no idea.
我以为你披枕头套是在模仿《快乐的修女》
That pillowcase thing, I thought you were doing "The Flying Nun".
有时候是啦
Sometimes we were.
别哭了
Come on.
你要帮我想想办法
You're gonna help me figure out what to do.
-场面蛮紧张的  -是啊
- Pretty intense, huh? - Yeah.
希望罗斯不会以为
I hope Ross didn't think we just went in there
我们是怕尴尬才进厕所的
because we were uncomfortable being out here.
希望他就是这么想的
I hope he did.
喂
Hello!
菲比  我是乔伊
Hey, Phoebs, it's Joey.
嘿  乔伊
Hey, Joey!
我在地铁看到一个很像你的人
I saw someone that looks just like you on the subway.
我正想过去打招呼
I was gonna go over and say hi,
又想到他不会在乎他长得像你
then I figured he doesn't care he looks like you.
你刚才浪费了四块钱
That just cost me 4 bucks.
我就是想问问小鸡小鸭怎么样了
Listen, I just called to see how the chick and the duck are doing.
它们跟菲比阿姨玩得很开心
They're having fun with Aunt Phoebe.
瑞秋阿姨根本没帮什么忙
Aunt Rachel hasn't been helpful at all.
你想我吗
So do you miss me?
有点  但我玩得太高兴了
Kind of, but I've been having way too much fun.
你还没想家
You're not homesick yet?
没有  应该没有
No, I don't think so.
我们七个都很想你
Well, the seven of us miss you.
-哪七个  -我  瑞秋
- Who's seven? - Me, Rachel
鸡鸭  宝宝们
the birds, the babies.
宝宝们也想我呀
The babies miss me?
披萨外卖来了
Pizza guy's here!
你们趁我不在的时候叫披萨啊
You ordered pizza without me?
对  但我们有在想你啊
Yeah, but we were thinking about you.
我们点了欢乐套餐
We ordered the Joy Special.
两个披萨
Two pizzas?
-对  我得挂了  回聊哈  -等下
- Yeah. Okay, gotta go! Talk to you later. - Wait!
等等  你们叫的哪一家的
Wait. Where did you get it from?
莫妮卡  你带我来这里干什么
Monica, why have you brought me here of all places?
等着瞧
You'll see.
我跟你说吧  这婚肯定是没法结了
I tell you, this wedding is not gonna happen.
罗斯
Ross.
怎么样  但假想一下有更多灯泡
Okay? But imagine a lot more lights
更少砖瓦
and fewer bricks
还有鲜花蜡烛
and flowers and candles.
乐队可以坐在这里
And the musicians, they can go over here.
椅子可以朝这边  然后
The chairs can face this way and...
你来说
You go.
不过要是你不喜欢
But if you don't love this,
我们就改别的时间别的地点
we'll do it any other place any other time.
真的没关系
Really, it's fine.
你高兴就好
Whatever you want.
这样很完美
It's perfect.
我不知道  要是下雨
And, I don't know, if it rains...
那就淋湿吧
Then we'll get wet.
我连个对象都没有
I don't even have a date.
-菲比  -什么事
- Phoebs. - Yeah?
你记得鸭饲料在哪里吗
Do you remember where the duck food is?
记得  在男生房间的水槽下面  怎么了
Yeah, it's in the guys' apartment, under the sink. Why?
因为我要去伦敦
Because I'm going to London.
什么  什么叫你要去伦敦
What? What do you mean you're going to London?
我得告诉罗斯我爱他
I have to tell Ross I love him.
亲爱的  你多保重
Now honey, you take care
孩子要等我回来再生
and you don't have the babies till I get back.
你不能去  罗斯爱的是艾蜜莉
Rachel, you can't go. Ross loves Emily.
我知道  我都知道
I know, I know. I know he does.
但我得把心里话告诉他
but I have to tell him how I feel.
他应该知道所有状况
He deserves all of the information
才好做出合适的决定
and then he can make an informed decision.
你去才不是为了这个呢
It's not why you are going.
你去是希望他说
You're going because you hope he's gonna say,
"我也爱你  瑞秋
"I love you too, Rach.
不管那个英国妞了"
Forget the British chippy."
你觉得他会这么说吗
You think he will?
不会  因为他爱那个英国妞
No, because he's in love with the British chippy!
瑞秋  如果你去的话  只会让他心烦意乱
Rachel, if you go, you're just gonna mess with his head
毁了他的婚礼
and ruin his wedding.
太迟了  你错过机会了
You know it's too late! You missed your chance.
抱歉  我知道你一定很难受
I'm sorry. I know this must be hard.
但已经结束了
But it's over.
不  在有人说"我愿意"之前都不算结束
You know what? No, it's not over until someone says, "I do."
我愿意  我愿意
I do! I do!
真懒得追你  我怀了一窝娃呢
Like I can really chase you. I'm carrying a litter!